

A Zwieseler Str. 40a, 10318 Berlin

After my psychology studies and a good two years in family support, I ended up as a digital marketer in one of the largest communications agencies in the world, where I brought my dormant creative streak to life and continued to live out my passion for psychology.

After 2+ years of steep growth curve to Senior Associate, due to private life circumstances I am now looking for challenges as a digital marketer in Germany.

# **Experience**

#### Digital Media Buyer | GIIR Germany GmbH - HS Ad, Frankfurt

May 2023 - Present

- · Creation, implementation and optimization of display, native, and video campaigns
- Creation and optimization of paid social media campaigns on various channels such as Instagram, LinkedIn, and TikTok
- Design and implement search engine advertising (SEA) and search engine optimization (SEO)
- Development and formalization of social media, programmatic and SEM strategies
- Monitoring of costs and return on investment (ROI/ROAS)
- · Leveraging all available GA4 data and analytics tools to determine campaign effectiveness and continuously drive better results
- · Collaborate with other teams and partners to implement campaigns, create reports, and build long-term relationships

#### Senior Associate | Xaxis - WPP, New York

Oct 2021 - July 2023

- Successful implementation of programmatic advertising strategies using industry best practices and achieving measurable results.
- Implement and manage DCO, cookieless, and identity solutions with practical application for campaign success
- · Analyze data and identify correlations between SEA, social media, display advertising, content marketing and other media channels to optimize overall marketing performance
- · Work closely with interdisciplinary teams to ensure smooth execution of campaigns and achieve common goals
- · Attention to detail and precision when working with numbers, to ensure accuracy in data analysis and reporting

#### Associate | Xaxis - WPP, New York

Feb 2021 - Oct 2021

- Setup and launch of campaigns in media buying platforms (DSPs).
- Extensive communication, rapid response and escalation of urgent matters to Senior Support.
- · Execute all aspects of campaign maintenance, including proactive performance reviews and optimizations, pacing and profitability updates
- · Assist with campaign analysis, deriving insights from data and making strategic recommendations to improve campaign performance and pacing

### **Education**

### Hunter College, New York

· Bachelor's Degree in Psychology

#### *Jan 2018 - May 2019*

### Borough of Manhattan Community College, New York

• Associate Degree in Psychology

#### Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

### **Achievements**

- Fastest ever promoted senior associate at Xaxis within 8 months
- Responsible for budget volumes ranging from \$4 million to \$20 million per year
- Achieved ROI of 500% per year for UPS
- Completion of the McKinsey Hispanic & Latino Leadership Program

# **Skills**

- Analytical thinking
- Data analysis
- Campaign optimization
- Interdisciplinary collaboration
- Attention to detail

- A/B Testing
- Programmatic Media Buying
- Social Media Buying
- B2B & B2C Marketing
- Billing Process

## **Platforms**

- The Trade Desk | Expert
- META | Advanced
- Salesforce | Advanced
- DV360 | Advanced
- Google Ads | Advanced
- Amazon DSP | Advanced

- GA4 | Advanced
- Python | Advanced
- Django | Advanced
- SQL | Advanced

# Languages

- English | Native
- Spanish | Native

• German | A2

#### Hobbies

- Running marathons
- · Teaching English and Spanish
- Screenwriting

- Hiking
- Traveling
- Cooking